

Contact

Argentina - Bs As - Belgrano

- (+54) 911-6880-8883
- in LinkedIn
- GitHub
- ─ Portfolio

Languages

ENGLISH

C2 (EF SET)

RUSSIAN

NATIVE

SPANISH

NATIVE

Skills

















Constantin Mitrokhin

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

Summary

Full stack developer with experience in process analysis, design and implementation, problem solving, and system testing. Solid knowledge in Node.js, JavaScript, Redux, React, Express, Sequelize, SQL, HTML and CSS. Strong problem-solving and analytical skills. Continuously learning and updating in new technologies.

Soft Skills

- Effective Communication
- Problem Solving
- Creative Thinking
- Adaptability
- Analytical Skills
- Teamwork
- Attention to Detail
- Empathy

Work Experience

TRAINEE PROGRAM

Applaudo Studios SRL August 2022 -October 2022

• Trainee Program Participant Achievements: Gained knowledge in PHP, React, HTTP, CSS, Ajax, and integration with Wordpress to create custom themes for user needs. Also integrated with the embedded Database in WP Web API.

RM COBOL 85 DEVELOPER

Process Consultora April 1999 -October 2000

• Documented product specifications and followed company methodology to define specifications.

Developed integrations between MS Office and other systems. Provided technical support for the product and its developments. Achievements: Developed stock management and invoicing software for small and medium enterprises. Designed and implemented the graphic interface for the stock and sales Management System.

ENGLISH TEACHER

Freelance February 2017 -Present

Achievements: Designed and taught English courses based on Dmitriy Petrov's methodology, with a duration of less than 20 hours of classes, mainly focused on oral skills for beginner levels. Trained over 50 students in the gastronomy sector, who needed to attend to foreign customers and expected high tips in foreign currency.

Education

INSTITUTO ORT

Systems Analyst August 2020 -PRESENT

HENRY

Full Stack Web Developer November 2022 -March 2023

Intermediate degree obtained:

• Programmer Analyst.

Achievements: Recognized as a reference among classmates for assistance in database creation, mathematics, and logic. Acknowledged for problem-solving skills and dedication to studies, reflected in current GPA of 8.53/10.

Degree obtained:

• Full Stack Web Developer.

Achievements: During my participation in Henry's Bootcamp, I also worked on two projects: one personal and one group project. In the group project, I was responsible for the majority of the server and database development, using my skills in Node.js, Express, Sequelize, and SQL. I worked closely with the team to ensure that the project met the specifications and was delivered on time.

Additional Education

UDEMY

Universidad JavaScript -From Zero to JavaScript Expert! November 2022 -Present In this Udemy course, I am acquiring comprehensive knowledge in programming with JavaScript. I am developing projects, solving challenges, and conducting tests. In addition, I am learning in greater detail about Object-Oriented Programming, Arrow Functions, Callback Functions, Promises, Async, Await, HTML DOM Manipulation, TypeScript, Angular, and many other useful tools for developing modern web applications. This course is providing me with a solid foundation in JavaScript that will allow me to be a more complete and capable developer in my professional career.